ANDI SAIFUL (Full Stack Developer)

Enthusiastic Full Stack Developer experience, and a passion for creating efficient and scalable applications, I am confident in my ability to contribute effectively to team success through hard work, attention to detail and excellent organizational skills. Professional with proven troubleshooting and debugging capabilities for resolving complex technical issues. Responsibility and motivation to continue learning, as well as growing and excelling in the technology industry, especially FinTech.

Jl. Bangka VIIIF RT.004/012 No.42, Pela Mampang, Mampang Prapatan, Jakarta Selatan

andi.saiful3135@gmail.com +62878-8417-7717

Education

Nasional University / Bachelor of Information Technology

Sep 2016 - Apr 2021, Jakarta

GPA: 3.35/4.0

Skills

- Go Language
- PHP (Native, Laravel)
- Javascript (Vanilla, JQuery, ReactJS)
- SQL (MySQL, PostgreSQL, Microsoft SQL)
- NoSQL (MongoDB)
- Linux

- Git Versioning (Github, GitLab)
- Containerize (Docker)
- Elasticsearch
- Redis
- HTML & CSS

Experience

Izidata Indonesia / Full Stack Developer

Jan 2023 - PRESENT, Jakarta

- Develop Restful API using architecture microservice using Go Language.
- Develop web based application using framework Laravel integrated with PostgreSQL.
- Improved software performance by identifying and resolving bottlenecks in the code.
- Refactored legacy codebases for improved maintainability, paving the way for easier future updates.
- Enhanced UI/UX with intuitive interface design and responsive web applications.
- Consistently met project deadlines by effectively managing time and prioritizing tasks according to importance.
- Built databases and table structures for web applications.
- Developed reusable components that significantly reduced development effort on multiple projects.

Sinergi Insani Primanet / Full Stack Developer

Nov 2021 - Jan 2023, Jakarta

- Integrated third-party APIs to enhance functionality and improve overall UI/UX on web platforms.
- Develop web based application using framework Laravel integrated with MySQL.
- Refactored legacy codebases and improved maintainability.
- Reviewed code, debugged problems, and corrected issues.
- Designed and developed analytical data structures.
- Built databases and table structures for web applications.

Plaza Auto Prima / Full Stack Developer

Oct 2018 - Nov 2021, Jakarta

- Develop end to end using PHP programming with framework Laravel.
- Reviewed code, debugged problems and corrected issues.
- Adjusted software parameters to boost performance and incorporate new features on Microsoft Dynamics CRM.
- Boosted network, system and data availability and integrity through preventative maintenance and upgrades.

Teknika Sarana Gardian / Customer Service Certified

Sep 2012 - Oct 2018, Jakarta

- Troubleshooting and repairing hardware and make sure the end-user is using hardware running well.
- Configuration and installation of the server operating system.

Languages

- Indonesian
- English

Interests

- Swimming
- Hiking

Network

LinkedIn: @andiSaiful

GitHub: @sflandi

Instagram: @andi.sfl